A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20 FA292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Files, 1920-1993; 2; 242 Box(es)
  - Munn, Robert - 1963 - England - Physical Chemistry, 1963-1975 (Box 151, Folder 1213)
  - Munnich, Frank - 1967 - Germany - Economics, 1966-1978 (Box 151, Folder 1214)
  - Murphy, Cecil - 1947 - England - Social Security, 1939-1984 (Box 151, Folder 1215)
  - Murphy, Cecil - 1947 - England - Social Security, 1939-1984 (Box 151, Folder 1216)
  - Murray, Charles Henry - 1951 - England - Education, 1951-1979 (Box 151, Folder 1217)
  - Murray, John - 1935 - England - English Literature, 1935-1986 (Box 151, Folder 1218)
  - Murray, Keith - 1926 - England - Agricultural Economics, 1926-1988 (Box 152, Folder 1219)
  - Murrell, John Norman - 1956 - England - Spectroscopy, 1955-1984 (Box 152, Folder 1220)
  - Mustafa, Deniz - 1989 - England - Engineering Science, 1988-1989 (Box 152, Folder 1221)
  - Myburgh, Andre Cyril - 1950 - South Africa - Entomology, 1949-1975 (Box 152, Folder 1222)
  - Myles, James Robertson - 1931 - England - Chemistry, 1932-1986 (Box 152, Folder 1223)
  - Nag, Ronjon - 1989 - England - Business Administration, 1988-1991 (Box 152, Folder 1224)
  - Nairac, Jean Laurence - 1952 - England - Civil Engineering, 1952-1977 (Box 152, Folder 1225)
  - Nash, Eric - 1927 - England - Economics, 1927-1962 (Box 152, Folder 1226)
  - Nash, Pamela - 1982 - England - Music, 1982-1990 (Box 153, Folder 1227)
  - Nathan, Sarah Catherine - 1977 - England - Social History, 1976-1990 (Box 153, Folder 1228)
  - Neale, Alan Derrett - 1952 - England - Anti-Trust Law, 1951-1980 (Box 153, Folder 1229)
  - Nedzela, Michel - 1969 - France - Applied Research, 1969-1977 (Box 153, Folder 1230)
  - Nerurkar, Richard - 1987 - England - Political Science, 1986-1992 (Box 153, Folder 1231)
  - Neudecker, Tilman - 1973 - Germany - Biochemistry, 1972-1987 (Box 153, Folder 1232)
  - Neufeld, David - 1981 - England - Philosophy of Science, 1980-1986 (Box 153, Folder 1233)
  - Neville-Jones, Lillian Pauline - 1961 - England - English History, 1960-1987 (Box 153, Folder 1234)
  - Newbolt, Thomas - 1981 - England - Painting, 1981-1989 (Box 154, Folder 1235)
  - Newman, Keith - 1975 - England - Aeronautics, 1974-1988 (Box 154, Folder 1236)
  - Newton-King, Pierce - 1958 - England - International Relations, 1958-1968 (Box 154, Folder 1237)
  - Nicholas, Herbert - 1935 - England - History, 1935-1989 (Box 154, Folder 1238)
  - Nicholas, Herbert - 1935 - England - History, 1935-1989 (Box 154, Folder 1239)
  - Nicholls, Peter - 1968 - Australia - Film Direction and Writing, 1968-1985 (Box 154, Folder 1240)
  - Nickson, Graham - 1976 - England - Painting, 1976-1985 (Box 155, Folder 1241)
  - Nickson, Graham - 1976 - England - Painting, 1976-1985 (Box 155, Folder 1242)
  - Nicol, Andrew - 1973 - England - Law, 1972-1986 (Box 155, Folder 1243)
  - Nicoll, Martin - 1982 - England - Zoology, 1981-1989 (Box 155, Folder 1244)
  - Nicoll, Martin - 1982 - England - Zoology, 1981-1989 (Box 155, Folder 1245)
  - Nicolson, John Mackenzie - 1984 - Scotland - Political Science, 1983-1988 (Box 155, Folder 1246)
  - Nimmerman, Peter - 1968 - Germany - Informal Education and Community Organization, 1967-1972 (Box 155, Folder 1247)
  - Nixon, Christine - 1984 - Australia - Political Science, 1984-1986 (Box 156, Folder 1248)
  - Nolan, Sidney Robert - 1958 - Australia - Painting, 1957-1986 (Box 156, Folder 1249)
  - Norman, Robert - 1956 - New Zealand - Civil Engineering, 1955-1987 (Box 156, Folder 1250)
  - Norris, Sydney - 1968 - England - Criminology, 1968-1988 (Box 156, Folder 1251)
  - Norris, William Tobias - 1969 - England - Engineering, 1958-1988 (Box 156, Folder 1252)
  - Northcott, Douglas - 1946 - England - Mathematics, 1938-1975 (Box 156, Folder 1253)
  - Norval, Ian - 1936 - England - Plant Pathology, 1936-1983 (Box 156, Folder 1254)
  - Notcutt, Bernard - 1931 - England - Philosophy, 1931-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1255)
  - Nott, Philip - 1980 - Australia - Business Administration, 1979-1987 (Box 156, Folder 1256)
  - Nowell-Smith, Patrick - 1937 - England - Philosophy, 1937-1987 (Box 157, Folder 1257)
  - Nunziante, Gianni - 1961 - Italy - Law, 1960-1975 (Box 157, Folder 1258)
  - Nurser, John Shelley - 1956 - England - Theology, 1955-1986 (Box 157, Folder 1259)
  - Nuttall, Alexander - 1930 - England - Engineering, 1930-1985 (Box 157, Folder 1260)
  - Nutton, Richard - 1982 - England - Surgery, 1981-1987 (Box 157, Folder 1261)
  - Nyssen, Ute - 1964 - Germany - American Drama and Theatre, 1964-1985 (Box 157, Folder 1262)
  - O'Brien, Karen Elisabeth - 1989 - England - English, 1988-1990 (Box 157, Folder 1263)
  - O'Brien, William Terrance - 1968 - Australia - Engineering, 1968-1980 (Box 157, Folder 1264)
  - O'Conner, Daniel - 1946 - England - Logic, 1946-1981 (Box 158, Folder 1265)
  - O'Driscoll, Elliot - 1957 - Australia - Geology, 1957-1985 (Box 158, Folder 1266)
  - O'Faolin, Sean - 1926 - Ireland - Literature, 1926-1986 (Box 158, Folder 1267)
  - Offe, Claus - 1969 - Germany - Sociology, 1968-1975 (Box 158, Folder 1268)
  - Ogston, Walter - 1946 - England - Engineering, 1946-1975 (Box 158, Folder 1269)
  - Oliver, Alexander - 1968 - England - Business Administration, 1967-1978 (Box 158, Folder 1270)
  - Oliver, Richard - 1927 - Scotland - Educational Psychology, 1927-1990 (Box 158, Folder 1271)
  - Oliver, Richard - 1927 - Scotland - Educational Psychology, 1927-1990 (Box 158, Folder 1272)
  - Ong, Guan Bee - 1956 - Malaysia - Medicine, 1956-1987 (Box 159, Folder 1273)
  - Onitiri, Herbert Maurice - 1956 - Nigeria - International Trade and Economic Development, 1956-1975 (Box 159, Folder 1274)
  - Oppenheim, Alexander - 1927 - England - Mathematics and Statistics, 1927-1987 (Box 159, Folder 1275)
  - O'Riordan, Timothy - 1963 - Scotland - Environmental Management, 1963-1986 (Box 159, Folder 1276)
  - Orr, Gordon - 1961 - New Zealand - Law, 1960-1980 (Box 159, Folder 1277)
  - Osbourne, Donald - 1950 - England - Physics, 1950-1986 (Box 159, Folder 1278)
  - Osbourne, Robert Vinden - 1951 - England - Literature, 1950-1975 (Box 159, Folder 1279)
  - Osgood, Stephen - 1963 - England - Architecture, 1963-1990 (Box 159, Folder 1280)
  - Osgood, Thomas - 1925 - England - Physics and Astronomy, 1925-1985 (Box 159, Folder 1281)
  - Osmotherly, Edward - 1972 - England - Tax Policy, 1972-1988 (Box 160, Folder 1282)
  - Osti, Aldo - 1956 - Italy - Economics, 1956-1976 (Box 160, Folder 1283)
  - Ovens, David - 1952 - England - Economics, 1951-1990 (Box 160, Folder 1284)
  - Owen, Marc Ellis - 1985 - England - Business Administration, 1984-1988 (Box 160, Folder 1285)
  - Owen, Marjorie - 1927 - England - Law, 1927-1932 (Box 160, Folder 1286)
  - Owen, Richard Charles - 1971 - England - Literature, 1971-1989 (Box 160, Folder 1287)
  - Owen, Walter Shephard - 1951 - England - Metallurgy, 1950-1987 (Box 160, Folder 1288)
  - Owen, William Thomas - 1934 - England - Literature, 1934-1990 (Box 160, Folder 1289)
  - Ozdowski, Seweryn Antoni - 1985 - Australia - Human Rights, 1984-1986 (Box 161, Folder 1290)
  - Pace, James - 1932 - England - Chemistry, 1932-1967 (Box 161, Folder 1291)
  - Paci, Massimo - 1965 - Italy - Sociology, 1964-1975 (Box 161, Folder 1292)
  - Parfit, Derek - 1964 - England - Philosophy, 1964-1986 (Box 161, Folder 1293)
  - Parker, Lorna Mary - 1983 - England - Business Administration, 1983-1987 (Box 161, Folder 1294)
  - Parker, Peter - 1950 - England - Industrial Relations, 1947-1990 (Box 161, Folder 1295)
  - Parkinson, Margaret Helen - 1974 - New Zealand - Nursing, 1973-1978 (Box 161, Folder 1296)
  - Parnell, George Wyndham - 1939 - England - Zoology, 1939-1941 (Box 161, Folder 1297)
  - Parry, Herbert - 1938 - England - Biochemistry and Animal Nutrition, 1938-1982 (Box 161, Folder 1298)
  - Parsons, William - 1959 - Australia - Agriculture, Fisheries and Wildlife, Forestry and Natural Resources, 1959-1987 (Box 161, Folder 1299)
  - Part, Antony - 1950 - England - Education, 1950-1986 (Box 162, Folder 1300)
  - Pascoe, Frederick - 1981 - Australia - History, 1980-1986 (Box 162, Folder 1301)
  - Pascoe, Frederick - 1981 - Australia - History, 1980-1986 (Box 162, Folder 1302)
  - Paterson, John Cargill - 1949 - England - Medicine, 1949-1970 (Box 162, Folder 1303)
  - Paterson, John Harris - 1948 - England - Political Geography, 1948-1976 (Box 162, Folder 1304)
  - Payne, William - 1956 - England - Climate Physiology, 1956-1985 (Box 162, Folder 1305)
  - Peacock, Martin - 1926 - England - Petrography, 1926-1954 (Box 162, Folder 1306)
  - Pear, Richard - 1939 - England - Political Science, 1939-1984 (Box 162, Folder 1307)
  - Pearse, Reginald - 1930 - England - Physics, 1930-1989 (Box 163, Folder 1308)
  - Pearson, David Charles - 1966 - England - City Planning, 1966-1975 (Box 163, Folder 1309)
  - Pearson, Harry - 1972 - England - Organic Chemistry, 1971-1988 (Box 163, Folder 1310)
  - Pearson, John - 1979 - England - Public Administration, 1979-1989 (Box 163, Folder 1311)
  - Pearson, Lucia - 1964 - England - Agriculture, 1963-1980 (Box 163, Folder 1312)
  - Peel, Richard - 1979 - England - Business Administration, 1979-1990 (Box 163, Folder 1313)
  - Pelizzi, Francesco - 1967 - Italy - Anthropology, 1966-1975 (Box 163, Folder 1314)
  - Penfold, Anthony - 1957 - Ireland - Architecture, 1957-1986 (Box 163, Folder 1315)
  - Penney, William - 1931 - England - Theoretical Physics, 1931-1978 (Box 163, Folder 1316)
  - Pepper, Christine Mary - 1978 - England - Pharmacology, 1977-1984 (Box 164, Folder 1317)
  - Peppiatt, Hugh - 1953 - England - American History, 1952-1975 (Box 164, Folder 1318)
  - Percival, Alan - 1936 - England - Mechanical Engineering, 1936-1976 (Box 164, Folder 1319)
  - Percival, Mary Eleanor - 1982 - England - Law, 1981-1986 (Box 164, Folder 1320)
  - Perrone, Luca - 1971 - Italy - Sociology, 1970-1983 (Box 164, Folder 1321)
  - Perry, Samuel Victor - 1948 - England - Muscle Biochemistry, 1948-1975 (Box 164, Folder 1322)
  - Peskine, Alain - 1967 - France - Architecture, 1967-1984 (Box 164, Folder 1323)
  - Peters, Werner - 1967 - Germany - American History, 1966-1986 (Box 164, Folder 1324)
  - Peterson, Arthur William - 1955 - England - Law, 1955-1986 (Box 165, Folder 1325)
  - Peterson, Arthur William - 1955 - England - Law, 1955-1986 (Box 165, Folder 1326)
  - Petti, Anthony - 1959 - England - History, 1958-1985 (Box 165, Folder 1327)
  - Pezzy, John Charles Vincent - 1987 - England - Economics, 1986-1990 (Box 165, Folder 1328)
  - Phillips, Derek - 1952 - England - Architecture, 1951-1985 (Box 165, Folder 1329)
  - Phillips, Derek - 1952 - England - Architecture, 1951-1985 (Box 165, Folder 1330)
  - Phillips, Gilbert Paul - 1949 - Australia - Agricultural Economics, 1947-1986 (Box 165, Folder 1331)
  - Phillips, John - 1957 - England - Endocrinology, 1956-1987 (Box 166, Folder 1332)
  - Phillips, Leon Francis - 1967 - New Zealand - Physical Chemistry, 1966-1975 (Box 166, Folder 1333)
  - Phillips, Peter - 1964 - England - Painting, 1964-1984 (Box 166, Folder 1334)
  - Phillips, Richard - 1970 - England - Plant Physiology, 1970-1975 (Box 166, Folder 1335)
  - Pickles, Alan - 1950 - England - Acoustics, 1950-1975 (Box 166, Folder 1336)
  - Picon, Francois Rene - 1974 - France - Anthropology, 1971-1986 (Box 166, Folder 1337)
  - Pilling, Joseph - 1972 - England - Race Relations, 1971-1988 (Box 166, Folder 1338)
  - Pimlott, John - 1947 - England - Public Relations, 1947-1968 (Box 167, Folder 1339)
  - Pinsent, Audrey Jane - 1949 - England - Microbiology, 1949-1975 (Box 167, Folder 1340)
  - Pipeleers, Daniel - 1973 - Belgium - Diabetes Research, 1972-1984 (Box 167, Folder 1341)
  - Pitteway, Michael Lloyd Victor - 1959 - England - Computer Science, 1958-1985 (Box 167, Folder 1342)
  - Plank, Charles - 1938 - England - Engineering, 1938-1970 (Box 167, Folder 1343)
  - Plowden, William Julius - 1958 - England - Political Science, 1957-1989 (Box 167, Folder 1344)
  - Plush, Vincent - 1981 - Australia - Music, 1980-1985 (Box 167, Folder 1345)
  - Plush, Vincent - 1981 - Australia - Music, 1980-1985 (Box 167, Folder 1346)
  - Pocock, Edward - 1958 - Australia - International Relations, 1957-1986 (Box 167, Folder 1347)
  - Pode, John - 1964 - England - Chemical Education, 1963-1982 (Box 168, Folder 1348)
  - Pole, Jack Richon - 1956 - England - History, 1955-1989 (Box 168, Folder 1349)
  - Poli, Bernard - 1962 - Algeria - American Literature, 1962-1982 (Box 168, Folder 1350)
  - Polkinghorne, John Charlton - 1955 - England - Physics, 1954-1989 (Box 168, Folder 1351)
  - Pool, Phillipa - 1967 - England - Psychology, 1966-1985 (Box 168, Folder 1352)
  - Porteous, Katrina - 1982 - England - Creative Writing, 1981-1988 (Box 168, Folder 1353)
  - Porter, Arthur - 1937 - England - Electrical Engineering, 1937-1987 (Box 168, Folder 1354)
  - Posthumus, Miejes-Herman - 1952 - Netherlands - Political Science, 1952-1986 (Box 168, Folder 1355)
  - Poston, Lindsay - 1982 - England - Business Administration, 1981-1986 (Box 169, Folder 1356)
  - Potok, Thierry - 1975 - France - Business Administration, 1975-1985 (Box 169, Folder 1357)
  - Potter, Harold - 1933 - Scotland - Mathematics, 1933-1988 (Box 169, Folder 1358)
  - Potter, Stephen - 1973 - England - Organic Chemistry, 1972-1986 (Box 169, Folder 1359)
  - Poulton, Harold - 1950 - Australia - International Air Law, 1949-1983 (Box 169, Folder 1360)
  - Poutasi, Karen Olive - 1984 - New Zealand - Public Health, 1984-1986 (Box 169, Folder 1361)
  - Powell, Edward - 1979 - England - Legal History, 1978-1989 (Box 169, Folder 1362)
  - Power, Desmond - 1969 - Australia - Special Education, 1969-1987 (Box 170, Folder 1363)
  - Power, Edwin - 1953 - England - Theoretical Physics, 1953-1987 (Box 170, Folder 1364)
  - Poznansky, Joel Benjamin - 1984 - England - Business Administration, 1983-1990 (Box 170, Folder 1365)
  - Poznansky, Mark Coleman - 1989 - England - Biological Science, 1988-1989 (Box 170, Folder 1366)
  - Preston, Harley H. - 1967 - Australia - Museum Administration and Art History, 1966-1979 (Box 170, Folder 1367)
  - Preston, Richard - 1933 - England - History, 1933-1984 (Box 170, Folder 1368)
  - Pretorious, Stephanus - 1930 - South Africa - Economics and Statistics, 1930-1982 (Box 170, Folder 1369)
  - Preuschen, Karl - 1955 - Germany - American Literature, 1955-1975 (Box 170, Folder 1370)
  - Price, Derek - 1946 - England - Mathematical Physics, 1946-1983 (Box 170, Folder 1371)
  - Price, Francis - 1935 - England - Physics, 1935-1988 (Box 170, Folder 1372)
  - Price, Nicholas Charles - 1971 - England - Physical Biochemistry, 1970-1985 (Box 171, Folder 1373)
  - Price, William Charles - 1932 - England - Physics, 1932-1988 (Box 171, Folder 1374)
  - Pridmore, Henry Digby - 1958 - Tasmania - Statistics, 1958-1980 (Box 171, Folder 1375)
  - Priestly, Clive - 1967 - England - Education, 1966-1986 (Box 171, Folder 1376)
  - Prion Pansius, Charles - 1971 - Belgium - Law, 1971-1975 (Box 171, Folder 1377)
  - Prior, Elizabeth - 1983 - Australia - Philosophy, 1982-1986 (Box 171, Folder 1378)
  - Pross, Harry - 1952 - Germany - Political Science, 1952-1975 (Box 171, Folder 1379)
  - Pross, Helge - 1952- Germany - Political Science and American History, 1952-1987 (Box 171, Folder 1380)
  - Provost, Alison Jane - 1987 - England - Business Administration, 1986-1991 (Box 171, Folder 1381)
  - Pryce, Maurice - 1935 - England - Physics, 1935-1975 (Box 172, Folder 1382)
  - Pryde, George - 1926 - England - History, 1926-1958 (Box 172, Folder 1383)
  - Prysor Jones, David - 1972 - England - Political Science, 1971-1982 (Box 172, Folder 1384)
  - Pugliese, Enrico - 1967 - Italy - Sociology, 1965-1986 (Box 172, Folder 1385)
  - Puketapu, Ihakara - 1967 - New Zealand - Geography, 1966-1984 (Box 172, Folder 1386)
  - Pulling, Stella Margaret - 1925 - England - Literature, 1925-1980 (Box 172, Folder 1387)
  - Puls, Hans - 1937 - England - Physics, 1937-1978 (Box 172, Folder 1388)
  - Pumphrey, William - 1949 - England - Engineering Metallurgy, 1949-1989 (Box 172, Folder 1389)
  - Purdie, Donald - 1936 - England - Chemistry, 1936-1959 (Box 172, Folder 1390)
  - Purves, Clifford - 1926 - Scotland - Chemistry, 1926-1965 (Box 173, Folder 1391)
  - Putt, S. Gorley - 1934 - England - Literature and Drama, 1934-1990 (Box 173, Folder 1392)
  - Putt, S. Gorley - 1934 - England - Literature and Drama, 1934-1990 (Box 173, Folder 1393)
  - Puxley, James - 1929 - England - Economics, 1929-1987 (Box 173, Folder 1394)
  - Quigley, David - 1980 - England - Architecture, 1980-1988 (Box 173, Folder 1395)
  - Quin, Ann Marie - 1965 - England - Writing, 1964-1973 (Box 173, Folder 1396)
  - Quirk, Charles Randolph - 1951 - England - Linguistics, 1951-1987 (Box 173, Folder 1397)
  - Quirk, Roger - 1937 - England - Industry, 1937-1956 (Box 173, Folder 1398)
  - Rabeneck, Andrew - 1967 - England - Architecture, 1967-1982 (Box 174, Folder 1399)
  - Radice, Edward - 1933 - England - Economics, 1932-1975 (Box 174, Folder 1400)
  - Radstom, Par Kristian - 1956 - Sweden - Contemporary American Civilization, 1955-1956 (Box 174, Folder 1401)
  - Rainbird, Alan - 1965 - Australia - Atmospheric Sciences, 1964-1975 (Box 174, Folder 1402)
  - Raitt, Suzanne - 1983 - England - English Literature, 1982-1986 (Box 174, Folder 1403)
  - Ramage, Colin Stokes - 1953 - New Zealand - Tropical Meteorology, 1953-1986 (Box 175, Folder 1404)
  - Ranci-Ortigosa, Pippo - 1964 - Italy - Economics, 1963-1981 (Box 175, Folder 1405)
  - Rands, Bernard - 1966 - England - Music, 1965-1983 (Box 175, Folder 1406)
  - Rattray, Peter - 1969 - New Zealand - Biochemistry and Nutrition, 1969-1981 (Box 175, Folder 1407)
  - Read, John - 1946 - Australia - Film Production, 1939-1975 (Box 175, Folder 1408)
  - Read, Piers Paul - 1967 - England - Creative Writing, 1966-1988 (Box 175, Folder 1409)
  - Reay, Donald - 1937 - England - Architecture, 1937-1980 (Box 176, Folder 1410)
  - Reed, Colin Barry - 1963 - England - Engineering, 1962-1977 (Box 176, Folder 1411)
  - Rees, Adrian - 1983 - England - Physiology, 1982-1988 (Box 176, Folder 1412)
  - Rees, Neville Truscott - 1970 - England - City Planning, 1969-1988 (Box 176, Folder 1413)
  - Rees, Neville Truscott - 1970 - England - City Planning, 1969-1988 (Box 176, Folder 1414)
  - Regini, Marino - 1970 - Italy - Sociology, 1969-1984 (Box 176, Folder 1415)
  - Regini, Marino - 1970 - Italy - Sociology, 1969-1984 (Box 176, Folder 1416)
  - Reid, Alan - 1960 - England - Theology, 1959-1982 (Box 176, Folder 1417)
  - Reid, Alice - 1951 - New Zealand - Education, 1951-1984 (Box 176, Folder 1418)
  - Reid, Cyril - 1946 - England - Spectroscopy, 1946-1982 (Box 177, Folder 1419)
  - Reid, Kenneth - 1960 - England - Engineering, 1959-1984 (Box 177, Folder 1420)
  - Reifenberg, Ernst Robert - 1952 - Germany - Mathematics, 1952-1964 (Box 177, Folder 1421)
  - Rempoulis, Andrew - 1962 - Greece - Chemistry, 1962-1975 (Box 177, Folder 1422)
  - Renaud, Philippe - 1959 - Switzerland - Literature, 1956-1979 (Box 177, Folder 1423)
  - Revans, Reginald - 1930 - England - Physics, 1930-1990 (Box 177, Folder 1424)
  - Reynolds, Stuart - 1975 - England - Insect Physiology, 1974-1989 (Box 177, Folder 1425)
  - Rhodes, Douglas - 1957 - England - Biochemistry, 1957-1985 (Box 177, Folder 1426)
  - Rice, Anthony - 1962 - England - Marine Biology, 1962-1986 (Box 178, Folder 1427)
  - Richard, Claude - 1965 - France - American Literature, 1964-1980 (Box 178, Folder 1428)
  - Richards, Nigel - 1983 - England - Chemistry, 1982-1990 (Box 178, Folder 1429)
  - Richardson, Frederick Denys - 1937 - England - Chemistry, 1937-1983 (Box 178, Folder 1430)
  - Richardson, Mabel Margaret - 1931 - England - Botany, 1931-1956 (Box 178, Folder 1431)
  - Riddell, Roland - 1948 - England - Microbiology, 1948-1984 (Box 178, Folder 1432)
  - Ridley, Adam - 1968 - England - Economics, 1967-1990 (Box 178, Folder 1433)
  - Ridley, John Wallace - 1954 - New Zealand - Engineering, 1954-1975 (Box 178, Folder 1434)
  - Ridyard, Susan - 1985 - England - History, 1984-1987 (Box 178, Folder 1435)
  - Rieger, Wolfgang - 1952 - Germany - American Studies and Public Administration, 1952-1981 (Box 179, Folder 1436)
  - Rieger, Wolfgang - 1952 - Germany - American Studies and Public Administration, 1952-1981 (Box 179, Folder 1437)
  - Riordan-Eva, Paul - 1985 - England - Opthamology, 1984-1989 (Box 179, Folder 1438)
  - Rizzardi, Alfredo - 1956 - Italy - English and American Literature, 1956-1980 (Box 179, Folder 1439)
  - Robb, Richard - 1926 - Scottland - Mathematics and Statistics, 1926-1975 (Box 179, Folder 1440)
  - Roberts, Eric Richard - 1938 - England - Agricultural Biochemistry, 1938-1980 (Box 179, Folder 1441)
  - Roberts, John - 1967 - Australia - Palaeontology, 1966-1986 (Box 179, Folder 1442)
  - Roberts, John Heath - 1980 - Australia - Management, 1979-1986 (Box 179, Folder 1443)
  - Roberts, John Heath - 1980 - Australia - Management, 1979-1986 (Box 179, Folder 1444)
  - Roberts, John Morris - 1953- England - American Studies, 1953-1990 (Box 180, Folder 1445)
  - Roberts, Keith - 1951 - England - Physics, 1951-1987 (Box 180, Folder 1446)
  - Roberts, Lewis Edward - 1954 - England - Physical Chemistry, 1954-1985 (Box 180, Folder 1447)
  - Robertson, James Bruce - 1972 - New Zealand - Law, 1971-1975 (Box 180, Folder 1448)
  - Robertson, John - 1949 - England - Civil Service, 1949-1955 (Box 180, Folder 1449)
  - Robertson, John Fraser - 1960 - New Zealand - Public Administration, 1960-1985 (Box 180, Folder 1450)
  - Robertson, John Monteath - 1926 - Scotland - Chemistry, 1928-1962 (Box 180, Folder 1451)
  - Robiette, Alan - 1964 - England - Chemistry, 1964-1986 (Box 180, Folder 1452)
  - Robinson, Denis - 1929 - England - Electrical Engineering, 1929-1977 (Box 180, Folder 1453)
  - Robinson, John Vernon - 1963 - New Zealand - Engineering, 1963-1975 (Box 180, Folder 1454)
  - Robinson, Robert - 1927 - England - Chemistry, 1926-1980 (Box 180, Folder 1455)
  - Robson, Brian Turnbull - 1967 - England - Urban Studies, 1966-1975 (Box 180, Folder 1456)
  - Robson, Harry - 1936 - England - Architecture, 1936-1980 (Box 181, Folder 1457)
  - Rochester, George - 1935 - England - Physics, 1935-1988 (Box 181, Folder 1458)
  - Roddie, Ian Campbell - 1960 - England - Physiology, 1960-1990 (Box 181, Folder 1459)
  - Rodrigues, Christopher - 1974 - England - Business Administration, 1974-1989 (Box 181, Folder 1460)
  - Rogers, Claude Ambrose - 1949 - England - Mathematics, 1949-1979 (Box 181, Folder 1461)
  - Rogers, Elsie - 1925 - England - Architecture, 1925-1974 (Box 181, Folder 1462)
  - Rogers, Terence - 1967 - England - Physics, 1966-1980 (Box 181, Folder 1463)
  - Rollin, Bernard - 1937 - England - Physics, 1937-1964 (Box 181, Folder 1464)
  - Romanes, George - 1949 - Scotland - Neuroanatomy, 1949-1985 (Box 181, Folder 1465)
  - Romano, Sergio - 1952 - Italy - Political Science and Law, 1952-1979 (Box 181, Folder 1466)
  - Roope, Katherine Clover - 1964 - England - Contemporary Dance, 1963-1980 (Box 182, Folder 1467)
  - Roper, John - 1937 - England - Economics, 1937-1985 (Box 182, Folder 1468)
  - Roper, John Francis Hodgess - 1959 - England - Economics, 1959-1990 (Box 182, Folder 1469)
  - Rosamond, John David Charles - 1976 - England - Biochemistry, 1975-1987 (Box 182, Folder 1470)
  - Rose-Innes, Alistair - 1960 - England - Physics, 1960-1989 (Box 182, Folder 1471)
  - Ross, Angus Macfarlane - 1954 - England - English Literature, 1953-1988 (Box 182, Folder 1472)
  - Ross, Benjamin David - 1988 - England - Film Studies, 1987-1990 (Box 182, Folder 1473)
  - Ross, John - 1950 - Scotland - Epidemiology, 1950-1955 (Box 182, Folder 1474)
  - Rossi-Crespi, Giulio - 1965 - Italy - Architecture, 1964-1980 (Box 182, Folder 1475)
  - Rossington, Timothy - 1980 - England - International Relations, 1979-1989 (Box 182, Folder 1476)